pcspeedup.com 2018-11-09

# Privacy policy - PC Speed Up - Clean, optimize and get a faster PC now!

## Overview

Speedchecker Ltd (“We”) are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and we shall endeavour to use any information that you provide when using this website in accordance with this privacy policy. Our policy and processes comply with the European Union General Data Protection Regulation introduced in May 2018.

This privacy policy is written to ensure that you understand what information we collect, how we protect any information you submit to us, how we use it and your rights and choices.

We may amend this policy from time to time by updating this page. Therefore, we suggest you check this page occasionally to ensure you are aware of and are happy with any amendments.

## What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Collect It?

When you buy or use our products and services we may collect information from you as described below.

#### Information You Provide

We collect information when you register and voluntarily complete our online questionnaires and forms including signing up for newsletters we collect the information you enter.

This information includes, but may not be limited, to name, email address, messages and images that you send and any other information you include in one of our online forms.

#### Data we collect Automatically

We collect information about any orders that you place including but not limited to item information, price and payment method.

When you visit our site, we use cookies and automatic logging (see “Cookies and Log Files”) to collect information including but not limited to browser information, IP address, Location (estimated), site links.

When you conduct activities on our site (for example, when you download a product) we record what you downloaded etc.).

When you make use of our PC Speed Up software, we will collect your IP address, Wi-Fi and other Internet connection information, speed test results and information about applications that may start when Windows starts. Other technical information about your PC is stored locally so that you can make informed decisions about how to improve your PC performance.

The IP address information we collect is not associated with you or any other individual and, for this reason, is not Personal Information.

#### Data Collected from Our Payment Processing Partners

We may collect your name and contact details, details of your subscription to our services, and other information gathered by Cleverbridge our payment processor, and transferred to us, including your address. You can read more about the information collected by Cleverbridge, to whose website you will be redirected when making a purchase, by following this link: [Cleverbridge Privacy Policy](https://www.cleverbridge.com/760/?scope=opprivacy&id=1bbe1v6jXG) .

Our website financial transactions are handled through PayPal, our payment services provider. You can review the PayPal privacy policy at the following location [PayPal Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). We will share information with them only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments.

#### Aggregated (summary) Data

We may collect some data about your connection to help improve our service to you and others.

#### Cookies and Third-Party Data Collection

Some data is collected by third-party companies (such as Google Ads) that have content (ads) and links on our sites. Details on what this data is and how you can control it are included in detail at the end of this privacy policy.

## How Is Your Data Used?

#### Order Processing

The information we request at the time of purchase is essential for us to provide you with our products and services. The information may also be used as necessary to process future orders and renewals.

#### Our Software

Information about your Internet connection and start up applications is used to provide you with a history of SpeedTest results; to give you choices about which applications to run when Windows starts and to provide other information about your PC so that you can use our software effectively.

The information we collect when you use our software is used for statistical purposes and analysis for management purposes in order to administer the website or improve our products and services.

#### Marketing

Information collected during purchasing or using our website may also be used for marketing purposes. In this section we describe how this information is used with your continued consent.

Internal record keeping, and administrative purposes, and to inform you about our events, services or products, or other related information that we think would be of interest to you.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes or to customise the website according to your interests.

To communicate marketing messages, newsletters and details of our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications).

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes or to customise the website according to your interests.

You may at any time ask us to refrain from sending you marketing messages by sending us an email with the words UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject box or via our [Contact Us](http://pcspeedup.com/contact_us.aspx) page. Any marketing email you receive will also have the option to decline to receive further information of that type from us.

#### Information Sharing (Third Parties)

Your information will not be disclosed to any third party unless you have given your consent to such disclosure, or where we are compelled to do so by law. However, we may disclose your IP address and other identifying information to third parties in response to a claim for infringement of intellectual property, defamation or other unlawful activity where, in such a case, we have a duty to respond to legal enforcement authorities.

We may disclose summary statistics about our site visitors, clients and sales in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes. These statistics will not include any personally identifying information.

#### Lawful Bases for Processing

The lawful bases we use for processing your data depends on the Services and Software you use. We collect and process your data when:

  * It is necessary to provide and operate the Services and Software we provide and to offer support and other necessary features. This is a Contract Basis.
  * It satisfies our Legitimate Interests such as in the provision of aggregate anonymous data, to market and to promote our Services. This is a Legitimate Interest Basis.
  * You give us consent. This is a Consent Basis.
  * Needed to comply with a legal obligation. This is a Legal Obligation Basis.

## Your Rights

You have the following rights:

  * To be informed about the collection of your personal information
  * To have access to your personal information
  * To have inaccurate personal information corrected
  * To have personal information deleted
  * To request that the processing (use) of your data is restricted. This is not an absolute right
  * To obtain and reuse personal data across different services. This is the ‘Right of Portability’
  * To object to the processing of information. For example, to direct marketing.
  * To object to your data being used for automated decision-making and profiling. Note: we do not do this but this is one of your rights under the GDPR regulation and is added for your information.

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date and is being used not only in accordance with the law but with your full knowledge and cooperation. If you have any questions or wish to exercise any of your rights then please visit our [Contact Us](http://pcspeedup.com/contact_us.aspx) page, email us at support@pcspeedup.com or write to us at the address below.

When you want to contact us about your personal information we will first verify that it is you making the request. Normally this will simply be an email from us sent to the email address we have collected for you asking for confirmation of your request.

If you would like us to destroy information we hold about you, please let us know. However, please note that if you use any of our services which require you to provide personal information, deleting our records may mean that you will need to resubmit it to continue using such services.

#### Restriction – Contract Basis

When we collect information during purchasing of our goods and services this is collected on the lawful basis of ‘Contract’.  You cannot object to our collection of this information at this time but you can withdraw consent later and this does not affect your other rights.

#### Restriction – Legitimate Interests

When we collect information during your use of website and software it is collected on the lawful basis of ‘Legitimate Interests’. A consequence of this is you have no right to portability; this means you cannot take this information and use it elsewhere. Even though you have no right to this information we will deal with any request as best we can. However, a lot of the information we collect is anonymised (we cannot identify who the data came from) which means we can only send you information that we know to be yours.

Our Legitimate Interests Assessment is available on demand and includes our Data Protection Impact Assessment (DPIA).

## Sale of business

If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

## Cookies and Log Files

#### Cookies

Cookies are text files stored on your computer, and accessible only to the websites which create them. Our website may from time to time use cookies and log files for statistical analysis, to understand user behaviour, to administer the site, to tailor the information presented to a user based on their preferences, and to improve user experience. Any information gathered by our use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies; however, you may delete, or disable cookies by following the instructions at <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/>. Please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you disable cookies. Our website uses cookies to keep you logged in, so disabling cookies may impair your experience of the service. Further information about cookies can be found on the Interactive Advertising Bureau’s website [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Social Media

If you share our content through social media, for example by liking us on Facebook, following or tweeting about us on Twitter, or giving us a '+1' via Google Plus, those social networks will record that you have done so and may set a cookie for this purpose. In some cases, where a page on our website includes content from a social network, such as a Twitter feed, or Facebook comments box, those services may set a cookie even where you do not click a button. As is the case for all cookies, we cannot access those set by social networks, just as those social networks cannot access cookies we set ourselves.

#### Log Files

Our systems automatically gather some anonymous information about visitors, including IP addresses, browser type, language, and the times and dates of webpage visits. Unless otherwise indicated in this privacy policy, the data collected includes personally identifiable information and is used as described above, such as for statistical analysis, to understand user behaviour, and to administer the site.

#### Google Analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). The information generated by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Further information about Google’s privacy policy may be obtained from <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>.

#### Google Adsense

From time to time our website may display adverts delivered by Google. Google may store or retrieve a cookie from your computer when serving adverts, in order to display those which are more relevant to you. These cookies are used to record information including the number of times you have seen an advertisement but will not lead to the transfer of your name, contact details or other personally identifiable information. Further information about Google advertising, their use of cookies, and how to opt out, please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

## Security

The internet is not a secure medium. However, we take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorised personnel have access to user information. We use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us, and our database is hosted in a secure data centre. Whilst we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

## Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us. Owing to the global nature of the internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By submitting your information, you consent to these transfers. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use our site.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this privacy policy from time to time. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page. If the change in our privacy policy affects the use of your personal information we will use our best endeavours

## Contact Us

**Email:**[support@pcspeedup.com](mailto:support@pcspeedup.com)

**Contact Us:**[Contact Us](http://pcspeedup.com/contact_us.aspx)

**Speedchecker Ltd.**  
The Black Church  
St. Mary’s Place  
Dublin 7  
D07 P4AX  
Ireland
